It's time to celebrate because Paradise finally did it. Paradise launched their catsuits.
With long arms and long legs and I'm going to try them on today.
First I have to sweep the confetti together though.
Here I am wearing the first one, the full leather version, the classic version.
It was pretty easy to get into so usually for Paradise pants I'm wearing size small
And for the catsuit I'm also wearing size small and it felt a bit wider than the pants.
And also the arms were really easy to dress because they aren't as tight as the bodysuits from Paradise.
And the arms are really long and also the legs are really long so I definitely like that.
The overall body length I'd say I'm at the upper level.
I recommend it for everyone up to 1.75m but maybe not taller because as you can already see here
this seam should sit here under the boobs so it looks great on the Basler twins, the two founders
when it's here when they're obviously a bit smaller than I am but I think I can wear it too
also the back side looks really nice they got rid of their signature curved seam which they
have in the leggings and we have two straight seams here which is completely new but they
kept the v-shape here in the back so to have this nice booty cut also in the catsuit and I
I think it works pretty well.
I wanted to show you the plain version first so you know what you get but I'm going to
put a corset on top of it and open the zipper.
I think the Benno von Stein corset and choker are a perfect fit here, not too much but there's
There's something going on and the catsuit is really comfy so I can squat down and move
around and raise my arms.
This is the fabric you already know from the Paradise Pants.
So really stretchy, really comfy.
Definitely a catsuit I'm going to wear more often because it's easy to dress and stretchy
comfy.
All the points.
and I do have the ultra version I'm going to show you that in a second
just think closed is also a look I think it's a tie between open and closed zipper here with
this one since the color is not so high but rather low by the way I do have a discount
code for paradise for the whole product range so also applying to the catsuits
it's selling 10 and you get 10% off I will link it down in the description
text so make sure to click on it or use my code if you buy something at paradise
and I am going to change into the ultra version now and here I am again
change wearing the PVC version. It is a bit tighter than the 4-letter one. I
think it's because the PVC is less stretchy. I realized this with the
regular Paradise pants as well. So if you're between sizes I recommend sizing
up for the PVC one. But again once you're into it it sits and also the fabric is
going to widen a bit the more often you wear it the looser it gets and easier it gets to dress
both versions are in a sleeveless variant available as well so long legs but no arms
you can see that here and also really comfy and nice maybe something for summer when it's hotter
and you don't want to wear long arms. I put a belt on top of it and a matching golden choker.
I decided against the corset too because it was too much and also because I wanted to talk about
the aspect of a missing crotch zipper. So we have no crotch zipper here which is not as handy if
you want to go to the toilet for example. Especially if you wear a corset or a harness or a belt you
have to undress all the accessories too. The catsuit itself, undressing and dressing is pretty
easy so that is not a problem in my opinion to go to the toilet with but it depends on how many
accessories you stack on top of it. The more accessories the harder and more annoying it gets.
I'm also not sure if a zipper would interfere with this signature cut here in the back with the
and the booty 3d modeling shape so yeah I don't think like in general that
paradise is a brand to do crotch zippers but maybe one time in the future who knows
I'm also wearing a PVC bra underneath so I opened the zipper really low and I wanted
to try this jacket on top of it because it also has golden accessories and I thought hey that's a fit
Let me check.
Yeah, I think it's cool.
If you want to go out in winter, wear a jacket.
These are not thermal fabric catsuits, so it's the regular thin fabric, which I think
is better, because then you can wear it in summer and in winter with a jacket.
You could also just wear tights underneath if you have cold legs in winter.
Why doesn't it close tight?
Nice.
Again, I do have a discount code for Paradise.
So check that out.
I also have a lot of other Paradise videos on my channel.
They usually do pants.
But, you know, I'm really happy they did catsuits now.
because if you know my channel and you know me then you know that I have a lot
of catsuits, I wear a lot of catsuits, I do a lot of catsuit videos so really happy
that I could finally do this one after years of working together with Paradise
Living Clothes. The zipper again. Also good look. I prefer the four that I wore a tiny
even more than the PVC one. With that I will end my video. You can write a comment and tell me which
one was your favorite. You can leave a thumbs up and subscribe to my channel. You can check out my
Patreon if you want to support me. As I said use my discount code. It's in the description text
and I hope you enjoyed this video. I hope you are as excited as me about these catsuits
and I will see you in the next video. Have a nice day. Bye!